Saratoga Springs Open Space Project; Records apap155
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Programs and Issues, 1970-1972; 1981-1986; 1989-2002; 3; 4.36 cubic ft.
  - Saratoga Spa State Park, Park History, 1960; 1988; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 9)
  - Saratoga Spa State Park, "Park Literacy and Conservation", Phillip Dearden, Article, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 10)
  - Saratoga Spa State Park, Proposed Sale, Position Paper, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 11)
  - Saratoga Springs City Government, Address Lists, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 12)
  - Saratoga Springs Facts and Figures, Fact Sheets, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 13)
  - Saratoga Springs Master Plan, Correspondence, Memorandum, 1994; 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 14)
  - Saratoga Springs Master Plan, News Clippings, 1994; 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 15)
  - Saratoga Springs Master Plan, Plan, Amendments, 1987 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 16)
  - Saratoga Springs Master Plan, Reports, Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 17)
  - Saratoga Springs Planning Board, Correspondence, Diagrams, News Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 18)
  - Saratoga Springs Planning Board, Meeting, Agendas, 1993-1998 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 19)
  - Scenic Road Designation, Correspondence, Legislation, Memorandum, 1992; 1995 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 20)
  - Scenic Road Designation, Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 21)
  - Skidmore College, Map, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 22)
  - Smart Growth, News Clippings, Articles, Correspondence, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 23)
  - Smart Growth Publications, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 24)
  - State Park Conference, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 25)
  - South Broadway, Proposal, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 26)
  - Three Rivers Development Corporation, Mission Statement, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 27)
  - Tobacco Bonds, News Clippings, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 28)
  - Truck Bypass, Alternatives, Map, Proposal, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 29)
  - Truck Bypass, Applicability of Public Trust Doctrine, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 30)
  - Truck Bypass, Bar Association Position, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 31)
  - Truck Bypass, Bypass Bill, Correspondence, Legislation, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 32)
  - Truck Bypass, Bypass Options, News Clippings, Notes, Reports, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 33)
  - Truck Bypass, Capital District Transportation Committee, Memorandum, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 34)
  - Truck Bypass, City Council Meeting Minutes, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 35)
  - Truck Bypass, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 36)
  - Truck Bypass, Editorials, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 37)
  - Truck Bypass, Effects on Wildlife, Maps, Notes, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 38)
  - Truck Bypass, Legal File, Case Histories, Memoranda, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 39)
  - Truck Bypass, Maps, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 40)
  - Truck Bypass, News Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 41)
  - Truck Bypass, Notes, Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 42)
  - Truck Bypass, Opposition Background, Correspondence, Notes, Position Statements, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 43)
  - Truck Bypass, "Proposed City Wide Truck Route System, Department of Public Safety, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 44)
  - Truck Bypass, Republican Position, News Clippings, Newsletter, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 45)
  - Truck Bypass, Saratoga Bypass Task Force, Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Notes, Reports, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 46)
  - Truck Bypass, State Park Allies, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 47)
  - Truck Bypass, State Park Allies, Mailing List, News Clippings, Response Forms, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 48)
  - Truck Bypass, Truck Bypass Study, Legislation Expenses, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 49)
  - Truck Bypass, Truck Volume Analysis, Correspondence, Study, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 50)
  - Undiscovered Park Art Exhibit, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 51)
  - Undiscovered Park Art Exhibit, Programs, Fliers, Artist Biography, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 52)
  - Urban Open Space, Correspondence, Report, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 53)
  - Vineyard Open Land Foundation, Agreement and Declaration of Trust, 1970 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 54)
  - Walkable/Bikeable Communities Conference, Conference Materials, Notes, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 55)
  - Watershed Issues, Correspondence, Memorandum, Notes, 1983; 1995; 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 56)
  - Watershed Issues, News Clippings, Pamphlets, Newsletter, 1995; 1999-2001; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 57)
  - Watershed Issues, Studies, Regulations, Reports, 1993; 1996; 1999; Undated (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 58)
  - West Avenue Corridor Plan, Report, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 59)
  - Wiebel Avenue, Meeting Minutes, News Clippings, Flier, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 60)
  - Yaddo Artist Community, Annual Report, Board of Directors Marling List, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 61)
  - "Applause due for new partnership to presume butterfly"Saratogian, 1991 October 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 1)
  - "Wilton seeks land gifts for butterfly"Saratogian, 1996 October 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 2)
  - "Wilton site targeted for butterfly preserve"Saratogian, 1996 October 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 3)
  - "Discover Saratoga video premiers at visitor center"Saratogian, 1996 December 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 4)
  - "Discover Saratoga with a videotape"Daily Gazette, 1996 December 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 5)
  - "Homey Hotel prompts zoning change proposals"Saratogian, 1996 November 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 6)
  - "Lets Close Those Strip Mall Holes on Ballston Ave."Saratogian, 1996 May 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 7)
  - "Landmark Saratoga Restaurant will reopen"Daily Gazette, 1996 May 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 8)
  - "Coffee Shop Welcomes Competition"Saratogian, 1997 April 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 9)
  - "Loan program is opposed"Daily Gazette, 1997 April 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 10)
  - "Eddie Bauar Coming Downtown"Saratogian, 1997 April 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 11)
  - "Chain Stores Would Change Downtown's Unique"Saratogian, 1997 March 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 12)
  - "Opposed groups to meet, discuss downtown Saratoga"Saratogian, 1996 February 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 13)
  - "Roohan Realty will move from Union to Broadway"Saratogian, 1996 February 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 14)
  - "Area's only Fabric Store to close"Saratogian, 1996 January 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 15)
  - "Speaking Out: Counteracting Downtown Fragility", Jeff and Deane Pfeil Saratogian, 1996 January 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 16)
  - "Londons return to city with Patisserie"Saratogian, 1995 December 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 17)
  - "What Main Street Can Learn From the Mall"The Atlantic Monthly, 1995 November (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 18)
  - "What Main Street Can Learn From the Mall"The Atlantic Monthly, 1995 November (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 19)
  - "Broadway Store Closes Doors"Saratogian, 1995 October 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 20)
  - "Downtown, Malls must prepare for changing future"Saratogian, 1995 October 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 21)
  - "Traffic Pole an Eyesore on Broadway"Saratogian, 1995 October 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 22)
  - "Plan to Pump $2M into future of Downtown", 1995 September 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 23)
  - "Coordinate downtown's future together", Robert Bristol Saratogian, 1995 August 30 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 24)
  - "City Offers Year Round Riches", Robert Bullock Saratogian, 1995 August 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 25)
  - "Megamerchants Still Mugging Small Stores", Christian Science Monitor, 1995 July 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 26)
  - "Bookstores Rethink Retail Missions"Christian Science Monitor, 1995 August 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 27)
  - "Other Cities Offer Lessons for Downtown"Saratogian, 1995 August 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 28)
  - "Beyond Downtown", Supplement Saratogian, 1995 August 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 29)
  - "Klotz cares about Downtown"Saratogian, 1995 July 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 30)
  - "Downtowner's plans advance for 66-room hotel", 1995 July 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 31)
  - "Shades of meaning for city"Saratogian, 1995 July 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 32)
  - "S.S. emerges as fine urban site"Albany Times Union, 1995 July 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 33)
  - "Putnam St. ventures indicate what's in store"Saratogian, 1995 July 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 34)
  - "City's 'Gut' Shapes Up"Saratogian, 1995 July 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 35)
  - "Big Bookstores can be Bad"Saratogian, 1995 June 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 36)
  - "Making City Spic and Span"Saratogian, 1995 April 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 37)
  - "Broadway project on time...McTygue has doubts about future Brause property"Saratogian, 1995 April 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 38)
  - "Funds may give Spa city face lift", 1995 April 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 39)
  - "Make downtown visually interesting"Saratogian, 1995 March 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 40)
  - "Who Owns Downtown?" Supplement Saratogian, 1995 March 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 41)
  - "Nurture Downtown for the future"Saratogian, 1994 November 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 42)
  - "Saratoga board Oks downtown retail plaza"Daily Gazette, 1994 November 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 43)
  - "Town Officials: More trees, less concrete"Post Star, 1994 June 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 44)
  - "Planner imagines Saratoga Springs as Walker friendly"Saratogian, 1994 May 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 45)
  - "Wising up downtown", 1994 March 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 46)
  - "Growth-related issues are healing problems for Saratoga County"Saratogian, 1994 March 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 47)
  - "Reviving Downtown, Series on Saratoga"Sunday Gazette, 1993 November 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 48)
  - "City needs Revitalization", 1992 April 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 49)
  - "Planned growth essential and save Spa city character", 1990 March 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 50)
  - "Cities hire retail consultants to improve on image", Capital District Business Review, 1989 July 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 51)
  - "Saratoga board asks developer to clean property"Daily Gazette, 1996 May 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 52)
  - "O'Hara Sees Resort as Riskiest Venture Yet"Daily Gazette, 1997 May 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 53)
  - "O'Hara resort would be largest in area"Saratogian, 1997 May 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 54)
  - "Mega Resort on the Drawing Board Daily Gazette, 1997 May 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 55)
  - "Local Bank Plans New Branch"Saratogian, 1997 May 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 56)
  - "Senior Housing Proposed, Tom's Lodge"Daily Gazette, 1997 April 4 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 57)
  - "Smaller Projects Working Best for Downtown"Saratogian, 1997 April 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 58)
  - "Downtown Motel Won't be Razed After-all"Saratogian, 1997 March 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 59)
  - "Meeting Mischaracterized", 1997 March 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 60)
  - "Tom's Lodge Proposal was Sacrificed to Political Plans"Saratogian, 1997 March 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 61)
  - "EOC Withdraws Housing Plans for Tom's Lodge"Saratogian, 1997 March 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 62)
  - "Blackmer Building has Rich History"Saratogian, 1997 March 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 63)
  - "Tom's Lodge Proposal Good for West Side"Saratogian, 1997 March 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 64)
  - "Old Supermarket Sites Hinger for Development"Daily Gazette, 1997 March 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 65)
  - "Renovations Underway at Arts Center but Building Already in Use"Saratogian, 1997 March 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 66)
  - "Saratoga Pushes Cluster Developments"Daily Gazette, 1997 February 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 67)
  - "City Developers Prove Revitalization Best Done One Project at a Time", Editorial Saratogian, 1997 February 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 68)
  - "Don't Stop Area Development"Saratogian, 1997 February 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 69)
  - "Don't Let Cars Rule City's Design"Saratogian, 1997 February 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 70)
  - "Kids' Box City Mirrors Modern Day Planning"Saratogian, 1997 February 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 71)
  - "County Weary of Regional Development Plan"Saratogian, 1997 February 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 72)
  - "Saratoga May Give Agency Walworth St. Lot for Office"Daily Gazette, 1997 February 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 73)
  - "A Few Small Steps by Brauses Better than None at all"Saratogian editorial, 1997 January 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 74)
  - "EOC looks to expand next to shelter"Saratogian, 1997 January 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 75)
  - "Absurd rule hurts city hotel project"Saratogian, 1997 January 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 76)
  - "Neighbor sues city over subdivision"Saratogian, 1997 January 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 77)
  - "City can build on momentum of 1996"Saratogian, 1997 January 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 78)
  - "Nurture City's Downtown", Letter to Editor Saratogian, 1997 January 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 79)
  - "Ace Hardware gets $525,000 from state"Saratogian, 1996 December 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 80)
  - "Why build over Spa County?", Editorial Daily Gazette, 1996 November 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 81)
  - "D'Andrea allowed to sell motel"Saratogian, 1996 December 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 82)
  - "Hospital might expand to exit 15"Saratogian, 1996 November 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 83)
  - Letter to Editor: "Let's get carousel into park"Saratogian, 1996 November 11 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 84)
  - "Developer plans 320 homes in city"Saratogian, 1996 October 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 85)
  - Editorial: "Israel plan for Franklin Square benefits city"Saratogian, 1996 September 23 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 86)
  - "Franklin Square to live up to name"Saratogian, 1996 September 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 87)
  - "South Broadway Master Plan"Daily Gazette, 1997 May 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 88)
  - "3 Ways to Improve the Downtown Landscape"Saratogian, 1997 May 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 89)
  - "New building to fill Broadway lot"The Saratogian, 1996 May 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 90)
  - "Council OK's growth for Southside, Saratoga Lake", 1996 May 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 91)
  - "YMCA plan seeks to build road in Pine Bush"Daily Gazette, 1997 April 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 92)
  - "Council must get involved in urban design"Saratogian, 1997 April 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 93)
  - "Approval recommended for Crescent St. Housing"Saratogian, 1996 March 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 94)
  - "Home may become Bed and Breakfast"Saratogian, 1996 March 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 95)
  - "Developer wants to put house in order"Saratogian, 1996 February 27 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 96)
  - "Franklin Square Building to be Renovated", 1996 February 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 97)
  - "Developers Question fee to tap water system for new homes"Saratogian, 1996 February 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 98)
  - "Housing plan approval delayed"Saratogian, 1996 February 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 99)
  - "Developer to make over Saratoga's Rip Van Dam"Daily Gazette, 1996 November 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 100)
  - "Downtown Tax District debates expansion"Saratogian, 1996 February 7 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 101)
  - "Wesley Project Could Enhance City's Atmosphere and Economy", 1996 January 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 102)
  - "Reader's Poll: Should Downtown Special Assessment District Be Enlarged?"The Saratogian, 1996 January 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 103)
  - "Video Store rental chain to occupy new building"Saratogian, 1996 January 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 104)
  - Editorial: Expand Downtown's Assessment District Saratogian, 1996 January 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 105)
  - "Housing complex units to cost at least $125,000"Saratogian, 1996 January 11 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 106)
  - "Business District May Be Enlarged", 1996 January 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 107)
  - "Downtown's future focus of forums"Saratogian, 1995 December 31 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 108)
  - "Public Debates Plan to Develop City Parking Lots"Saratogian, 1995 October 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 109)
  - "Development Decision Creates Critical Crossroad"Saratogian, 1995 October 17 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 110)
  - "In Defense of Putnam Square Project", 1995 September 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 111)
  - "Wise, Putnam plans rated tops", 1995 September 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 112)
  - "Downtown Projects to be rated", 1995 September 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 113)
  - "This Old House a revived gem", 1995 September 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 114)
  - "Address empty, unsightly land on S. Broadway", 1995 August 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 115)
  - "Seniors housing plan OK'd", 1995 July 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 116)
  - "Comfort Inn Plan gets OK", 1995 June 8 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 117)
  - "Expect bad impact from Crescent St. Housing project", 1996 May 16 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 118)
  - "City took over springs in 1912", 1995 January 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 119)
  - "S.S. gut becomes a developer's dream"Albany Times Union, 1994 December 25 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 120)
  - "Congress Centre takes off", 1994 November 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 121)
  - "Development needs public-sector booster", 1994 October 24 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 121)
  - "O.S.P. works to develop the city", 1994 October 24 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 122)
  - "City slates West Ave. workshop"Saratogian, 1994 July 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 123)
  - "Growth plan should have vision", 1994 July 18 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 124)
  - "Residents: Keep subdivision out"Saratogian, 1994 June (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 125)
  - "Downtown 5-story gets O.K", 1994 May 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 126)
  - "Stop rim development to save downtown"Saratogian, 1994 April 1 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 127)
  - "Mixed reviews for Saratoga County's suburban boom"Daily Gazette, 1994 March 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 128)
  - "Office building planned"Daily Gazette, 1994 March 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 129)
  - "Five-story building proposed downtown"Saratogian, 1994 March 5 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 130)
  - "S.S. wonders where it should grow"Sunday Gazette, 1994 February 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 131)
  - "Developers lament costly requirements for building in Spa city"Albany Times Union, 1994 February 2 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 132)
  - "Saratoga Springs should slow down development Saratogian, 1993 July 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 133)
  - "Spa City looks at West Avenue's future Saratogian, 1993 March (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 134)
  - "City should preserve, create open space"Saratogian, 1992 July 26 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 135)
  - "Open Space panel in Spa City aims to improve plaza"Daily Gazette, 1993 May 10 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 136)
  - "Railroad Place building a boost to downtown"Saratogian, 1994 May 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 137)
  - "Sprawl and Sense in Saratoga"Daily Gazette, 1993 December 9 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 138)
  - "Exhibit depicts architect's visions of the Saratoga Springs of the future"Saratogian, 1992 November 20 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 139)
  - "'Imagine Saratoga' just what exhibit wants you to do"Saratogian, 1992 November 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 140)
  - "New program will take care of city's trees"Saratogian, 1992 August 13 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 141)
  - "Conservation vs. growth center of master plan discussion", Record, 1992 May 19 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 142)
  - "Stop the development", 1992 April 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 143)
  - "Open Space is the key to our city's future", John DeMarco, 1992 March 6 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 144)
  - "Grand Avenue rezoning plan must be seen as part of whole"Saratogian, 1992 January 28 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 145)
  - "Grand Ave. property needs to be rezoned"Saratogian, 1992 January 22 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 146)
  - "O'Connell will ask to delay Grand Ave. rezone request"Saratogian, 1992 January 21 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 147)
  - "Lions Club gives $25,000 for ice rink"Saratogian, 1992 January 14 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 148)
  - "Mayor's capital budget melts ice rink plan"Saratogian, 1992 January 3 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 149)
  - "Economic Value of Open Space", Landlines, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 150)
  - "Year brings new arts center, loss of opera at SPAC"Saratogian, 1996 December 29 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 151)
  - "Charities say individual contributions can't make up for government cuts"Saratogian, 1996 December 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 152)
  - "Preserve Clifton Park's open space as part of larger master plan Saratogian, 1996 December 12 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 153)
  - "Hall of Springs, SPAC not bound to sell Coca-cola"Saratogian, 1996 November 15 (Box 3 (3-Programs and Issues), Folder 154)